Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[To My Shore]
The guy who molested me...
I found him.
- He's here, in this club.
- How did you find him?
Let's go hear what he has to say first.
I'll go scout ahead.
Who the hell are you?
- Young Master Bai.
- Turn the lights back on.
- I need a word with you.
-
- Clear the room.
- Who the hell is this?
- Weirdo.
- Who the hell are you?
- Young Master Bai,
I didn't expect it to be you in here.
- You know him?
- I do.
Met him at one of Shi Li Hua's parties.
What do you two want?
You barge in and start smashing things, huh?
What do we want with you?
You should know why we're here.
Since I've managed to find you today, I came prepared.
If you don't mind an audience, then neither do I.
Fine. Let's talk.
Everybody out. I've got real business to discuss.
Get another room heated up. I'll be there later.
- We'll be waiting, Young Master Bai.
- We'll be waiting, bro.
We'll head over first.
All right, talk.
Young Master Bai. We don't know each other well.
But we do have Shi Li Hua in common.
So, if you've got anything to say, measure it carefully.
And don't play coy.
President Fan, right?
What's your relationship with this gentleman who wants to talk to me?
- Friends.
- Oh, friends.
Young Master Bai.
Today, I'm here for an explanation.
With this chemistry,
if I hadn't personally got him to the bed,
I might believe they're just "friends".
He sure knows how to have fun.
Handsome. What're you on about?
What "explanation"? I don't follow.
Makes sense. You've done so many filthy things.
You can't keep track of them all.
Let me jog your memory.
Last Thursday night.
The Qiyue Hotel parking lot.
Then tell me...
What exactly did I do to you that night?
What the hell are you looking at?
I wouldn't be here without proof.
Young Master Bai.
If you've got no explanation, I'll assume it was you.
And I'm here to settle the score today.
How?
Simple.
An eye for an eye.
Whatever you did to me, I'll return in kind.
I'll return in kind.
Young Master Bai. How should we start undressing you?
- Screw you! I'm straight.
- Young Master Bai.
Watch your mouth.
Your phone's been ringing.
Take the call first.
Calm down. Then we'll talk.
Fan Xiao, how the hell are we supposed to talk?
We're not in a rush.
Take the call first.
Sit.
We'll talk slowly.
Hello.
Okay.
Fine, I admit it. I did it.
Why?
Why the hell do you think?
I took a little something. Got revved up.
No one was around.
You looked decent enough.
You carry ether on you?
And what if I do? It's my hobby, gotta problem?
Just say it. How much?
I don't want your money.
Then what do you want? What you just said won't fly.
Relax. I can't bring myself to put my mouth on you.
Give me ten minutes to beat you up. And then we call it even.
Fucking hell! You dare lay a hand on me?
I'll kill you today!
You dare hit me, huh?
I'll bust your head for free today.
You're swinging that at him? Say the word if you want to die.
- Fan Xiao, stop.
- Don't worry.
I won't take his life.
I'll handle the dirty work.
Ten minutes. Time me.
Fan Xiao, are you really doing this?
If we're acting, we should make it believable.
Thanks for your cooperation, Young Master Bai.
Fuck off. I'm done playing.
I'll spill everything.
Planning to give up Anna?
Shi Li Hua said you could
have her sleep with me.
Is that for real?
She's a beauty queen after all.
I'll have her come out to drink with you first.
Whether you can take her home
is up to your skills.
Then hurry, hit me quick.
I'll stick to exposed skin then.
Looks more real.
And you'll suffer less.
Apologies in advance.
Stop hitting me.
Any more and I'll be one foot in the grave.
Fine.
One last hit.
Remember to scream louder.
Fan Xiao. What are you doing?
The Bai family isn't easy meat.
Just scream.
What are you doing?
Tell me, will the person outside feel sorry?
I…
I don't know. No clue...
Young Master Bai. You must take the fall for this.
Remember what I said.
Offend anyone but Fan Xiao.
He'll smile as he toys you to death.
I should ask him for something good.
Thanks for your hard work, Young Master Bai.
Let's go.
Wait, your hand.
It's nothing.
I just hurt it when I worked that punk over.
Just hit the wall by accident.
No. You're going to the hospital.
[Episode 4]
Welcome to my humble abode, Director You.
Your right hand just got splinted. Don't move it.
Tell me what you can't do. I'll help you.
It's really nothing.
I'll do it.
You're a grown man, don't be stubborn.
Slow down.
Your metacarpal's fractured. And you call it "no big deal".
The doctor also said if this doesn't heal right, you'll have lasting problems.
Fan Xiao, you've been in Thailand for a while.
Why does your place still look like a showroom?
I'm mostly at the office.
I stay here only when I need
some peace and quiet.
You can check out the terrace.
- The view's great.
-
At night, only the mountain's
outline can be seen.
In the daytime, especially after rain,
it's beautiful.
Before you sleep, if there's anything you can't do one-handed,
just tell me.
This collar's a little tight.
Mind giving me a hand, Director You?
It's not like both of your hands are useless.
Use your left one.
Useless.
Don't move your right hand. Come here.
Come.
Slow down.
You really do care about me.
Zip it.
Chin down.
What are you doing?
I've been looking
for the curtain remote forever.
It was wedged in the sofa behind you.
Director You.
There are two buttons left.
There.
I'll change into a robe.
Fan Xiao, I think the person who molested me wasn't Bai Peng Yu.
How so?
Last time, I deliberately said "an eye for an eye" to test him.
But he clearly hates men.
He took something and was also drunk.
When you're that out of it, you don't care.
- You shouldn't drink on meds.
- I know.
This is for you.
Have a little to relax and sleep.
If you still have doubts, we'll keep digging.
I checked the lady boss who poured you drinks.
- It wasn't her.
- We'll see.
Either way, thanks, Fan Xiao.
Honestly…
From childhood to now,
few people have ever protected me like this.
What?
Do you know what the women
at our company say about you?
What do they say?
They say you're the brooding,
scheming male lead.
Anyone you latch onto has a bad end.
If they knew you were this childish and clingy,
what would they think?
You Shu Lang.
I don't care what they think.
I only want to know what you think.
It's late.
You won't get a cab here.
Don't go back for now.
I can't drive with this hand.
Tomorrow, I'll have to
trouble you to take me to work too.
The guest room has its own bathroom.
The bedding's new. No one's used it.
Treat it like a hotel for the night.
Keep the hand dry after you go home.
I'll prescribe antibiotics.
He may run a fever tonight.
Keep an eye on him.
Fan Xiao. Fan Xiao.
Fan Xiao.
Are you feeling unwell?
Shu Lang.
I am uncomfortable.
You said you'd help me.
Fan Xiao.
I'm just asking a favor.
No need to throw a punch if you disagree.
Fan Xiao.
I'm gay.
I can't play straight-boy games with you.
We're here. Out you go.
My top button It's been undone since we left.
Director You, you're really
just going to ignore me?
The Director You I know even helps strangers.
Why don't I get that treatment?
You still want my help?
Don't mind it, Director You.
Orientation is everyone's freedom.
Unless you're insecure?
No. I'm just afraid you'll...
You underestimate me.
It's just being gay.
Did you forget where we are?
Hello.
Gay marriage is legal.
So… the button?
Useless.
Come here.
Done.
So, your girlfriend is actually a man.
I didn't mean to hide it.
I'll introduce you sometime.
Go on, get out. I'm going to be late.
I can't hold back.
I want you.
Huh? What does that mean?
Wishing you a great day.
Huo, send the antique ring
from the auction to Lu Zhen.
It's time to give him a nudge.
So, you're breaking up with me and there's no other reason?
I'm not good enough for you.
You sure?
Mr. Lu, President Fan asked me
to bring these to you.
That's not right. I can't take gifts I didn't earn.
How can I let him continue sending such gifts?
Mr. Lu, I'm just following orders.
If you don't like them, take it up with President Fan.
Has he been busy lately?
Why is he always sending gifts through you?
Our boss is very possessive.
Take care of yourself.
I'm off.
Uncle You.
Lu Zhen. There's no room for me in your heart anymore.
Your workplace is complicated.
Protect yourself.
Uncle You.
You Shu Lang. Did you ever love me?
You're very good to me.
You're thoughtful, attentive.
But is that love?
You're a flawless boyfriend,
but I can't feel you.
Your joy, anger, and sorrow, I can't share in them.
When you're silent, when you smoke,
when you smile,
you feel alone to me.
Even with your arm around me, with you right by my side,
I still can't feel you.
I still feel you're alone.
No matter how I try, I can't get in.
Do you know?
That kind of defeat is truly crushing.
Director You, this booze is strong.
Don't chug it.
Why are you drinking? Your hand isn't healed yet.
- You can't drink.
- I'm not, it's fruit tea.
What's wrong? Bad mood?
Know how I can tell you're unhappy?
Because we're the same kind.
What kind?
People who wear masks.
So, you don't have to hide from me.
Have a smoke, it'll help.
I don't want one now.
Fine. Give it here.
What?
We've shared a half-smoked cigarette before.
You weren't this jumpy.
It's nothing.
- I broke up.
- What?
You must be kidding.
Weren't you fine a few days ago,
and said you'd introduce us?
Forget it. Have a drink with me.
I can't understand.
How could anyone let a good catch like you go?
Enough chatter.
Your hand isn't healed. Drink fruit tea.
Fine. I'll drink that.
I'll risk my life to accompany the gentleman.
Booze works.
Fruit tea.
Come on. Cheers.
If I get drunk, take me home.
Easy. Easy.
So heavy.
Director You, you're too precious.
Let me wash my hands first.
Didn't expect you to be so tender.
But you're just unlucky.
Always meeting the wrong people.
♫ ♫
Uncle You, your sweet-and-sour pork is amazing.
Love you. Mwah.
♫ ♫
What do I do…
I really want a bite,
but I can't leave marks on you today.
My Bodhisattva, did you descend to test me?
How about just a kiss?
♫ ♫
What did you say?
You Shu Lang is kissing me.
He's kissing me on his own accord.
He...
Zhen Zhen. Zhen Zhen.
♫ ♫
Fan Xiao.
Why is he here?
It's early in the morning.
- Men are easy to tease, Director You.
- Cut it out. Let go.
I'm not kidding.
Feel this.
Fan Xiao, that's not how you joke.
You're crossing a line.
Director You, then let me ask...
What happens if I cross the line?
I told you I'm gay.
If you keep pushing,
I'll flip you over and take you.
What?
What did you say you'd do to me?
What do you want to eat?
How long has it been for you, Director You?
Last night you were drunk, and chasing me for kisses.
I couldn't dodge.
Oh, right, your ex is called Zhen Zhen, right?
You kissed me and called for him.
Look, you broke my lip.
Wanna see?
It's just a kiss. What's the big deal?
But scaring me with that condom was on you.
What if I wasn't scared?
Get lost.
I took care of you all night.
If nothing else, that's effort.
No breakfast? And now you kick me out?
You're cold-blooded.
I'm showering, suit yourself.
Zhen Zhen,
how long till your boyfriend willingly gets into my bed?
Still getting calls from Lu Zhen?
You keep avoiding him.
Aren't you afraid he'll lose hope and run back to your dear Director You?
Knowing You Shu Lang, he'll never take him back.
Your move, hurry.
Bomb.
You toyed with You Shu Lang, and Lu Zhen took the stray bullets.
I don't know who to pity.
But then again, who can predict love?
An ex pouts, strips a little,
and turns on the charm,
few men can resist.
Bomb.
Look at my hand. Can it beat yours?
Vengeful, same at the card table.
You've never been in love.
You don't get how easily old flames reignite.
Speaking of, on that note, what's up with you and Anna?
She really is courteous with you, huh.
She actually went to see Bai Peng Yu.
Once, a rich guy slit his wrist
in front of her, begging her to come back.
Blood was everywhere. She didn't even blink.
In the end, the businessman himself
called the ambulance.
You two are menaces. Hurry up and get together.
Do the world a favor.
Buddha says nine kinds of people go to hell.
She and I, neither of us is getting out clean.
Come on, drink.
Come on, cheers.
Huo, for the team going to the industry expo,
add one more slot in the travel list.
Give it to You Shu Lang.
We've arrived in Thailand for a long time,
but we're always slammed with work.
It's great to finally have a chance
to see the beach.
Yeah. The scenery's great.
- White sand, palm shadows, so beautiful.
- That's why conferences now
often pick coastal cities, so you can unwind after work.
Here.
You all can eat. I've got no appetite.
Fan Xiao? What's wrong?
Maybe he's exhausted.
Want to take a walk on the beach together?
We can still catch the sunset.
I'll pass. I'm a little tired.
You go ahead.
Shu Lang, have fun.
Cure that broken heart.
Director You, shall we?
Okay.
Big brother, buy a flower please?
What a sweet mouth.
Your Chinese is great.
Sell out early and get some rest.
Thank you.
You're so thoughtful.
Fan Xiao said you broke up
with your lover today.
In our department, lots of girls fancy you.
I guess they've got a shot now.
Don't tease me.
He isn't teasing, I can vouch for it.
Every time your name comes up,
they get so excited
the boss has to cough to shut them up.
Can't blame them. You're handsome and attentive.
Good thing you're here,
especially with President Fan injured.
Otherwise,
none of us know him well, and wouldn't know how to look after him.
It's just work.
Tell you what, you two
continue with the stroll.
He barely ate today.
I'll take some food to him.
Sure, sure.
See you.
Don't turn on the light.
Please don't turn it on.
Fan Xiao?
What's wrong, Fan Xiao?
Let me hold you just for a minute.
It's okay.
I'm here.
I haven't been to the sea in a long time.
I'll get you some water.
Pour me a drink.
Okay.
You know the tsunami
that killed over 300,000 people?
You mean decades ago, the one in Indonesia?
My family was vacationing on an island.
Minutes before it hit,
I was eating sticky rice,
wrapped in lotus leaf.
For years after,
every nightmare carried that smell.
I just smelled it again.
I was back there, curled in my mother's arms,
shaking with fear.
Sorry, did I scare you?
It's okay.
Let me.
Shu Lang.
If it were you,
would you reach out to protect someone?
I'm not sure.
In a life-or-death situation,
no one knows how they'll act.
What if it's your spouse and child?
I wouldn't leave them.
Director You, I knew you were a good man.
At least you and your mother made it out.
She died.
Mom, the water is rising.
I'll hold you.
- Mom.
- Don't be afraid.
Are we going to die?
No, Xiao Xiao. I'm here.
It will pass. It'll be okay.
Mom, I'm scared.
I've got matches.
Hold this. And this, too.
If you get too scared, we'll light another.
In the end she used all her strength
to pile everything in the room into a corner
and had me stand on it.
I watched her sink inch by inch.
The last thing she said to me was...
Xiao Xiao, you have to live.
Is living that hard?
Living is the real pain.
My mother died right in front of me.
It was so dark.
I had only a box of matches.
Later, my matches ran out.
I couldn't see her.
Fan Xiao…
Mom…
Why did you keep telling me to live?
My matches are gone.
I want to go be with you.
This world is too dark.
I hate them.
I hate everyone.
They should all drown with you.
Fan Xiao.
Fan Xiao, calm down.
Calm down.
That tsunami is long past.
It's over now.
- Shu Lang?
- It's me.
I'm here.
Do you know...
You're the one I hate the most now!
Fan Xiao, breathe, calm down.
Calm down.
Who do you think you are to decide others' lives and deaths?
Who do you think you are?
A Bodhisattva who saves all?
Fan Xiao, calm down.
Then save me.
Fan Xiao!
Sorry.
- I just...
- It's okay.
I get it, trauma response.
Last time, I got drunk and crossed a line.
This time you were triggered.
We're even.
Let's not bring it up again.
You kissed me.
I kissed you.
Balanced, done.
The udon I packed is probably soggy.
I'll buy another.
Shu Lang.
Do you know why I forced your name
onto the travel list?
No.
Because I hope when I'm afraid, you're there.
When you're around, I'm calmer.
What?
You actually went to the coast?
Aren't you afraid of a relapse?
Already had one.
Fucking hell!
Then why do you sound so normal?
Director You is here.
And?
I can't run forever.
If I'm going to try to take a step forward,
might as well milk a little pity
in front of him.
That works?
You...
Noisy.
Distinguished business representatives,
please take a short break.
Our forum will officially begin in ten minutes.
Excuse me, could you please
help us adjust our seats?
I need a seat that isn't by the window.
All right. Let me coordinate it.
Thank you.
Excuse me, the sea breeze is too noisy.
Would you mind closing the windows?
First of all, I'm very happy to attend this WS-hosted summit.
Here, I see many old friends.
Thank you all for coming.
This forum is top-tier domestically,
and even in international medical
and technological exchange.
This expert is very forward-thinking,
with a global vision. Focus.
We have received strong support
from investors at home and abroad.
Well, thank you to the experts
for their wonderful speeches.
That's all for today's theme forum.
Everyone can go to the restaurant
to enjoy dinner.
Thank you, everybody. See you tomorrow.
Let's go. I ordered dishes.
Let's eat back at the hotel.
Shu Lang.
- What is it?
- Take a stroll on the beach with me.
You sure? It'll be dark soon.
You may not see the water...
but the waves will still...
I want to try.
Fan Xiao! Fan Xiao, come back.
Fan Xiao, stop.
What, afraid I'll kill myself?
Walk back, Fan Xiao.
If you want exposure therapy,
you can't rush it.
So, after the accident,
you never came back to the sea?
Afterward, I did on-and-off therapy for years.
As an adult, I thought I could face it.
So, I went to Phuket.
I didn't even see the ocean, but just hearing it sent me over the edge.
Later, I tried desensitization again, but it didn't help.
Slowly,
I got tired of being out of control.
I didn't want to face
the nightmare over and over.
In the end, I could only give up and run.
Like a coward. Will you laugh at me?
Fan Xiao, it's not like that.
Everyone has something they can't face.
You too?
I'm afraid to swim.
I actually used to be good at it.
I was very good at swimming.
Back then, we were poor.
We boys went to the river to set fish traps.
Another kid and I swam well, and we dared to set traps deep.
We caught more fish than others.
But slowly,
he saw me as a rival.
He started to resent me, and bullied my younger brother.
Once, he set the trap too deep.
When he dove to get it, his legs got tangled.
You saved him?
Yes.
I saved him, but he almost
dragged me down with him.
He panicked, and clutched my arms and legs.
Then a gulp of water knocked him out, and I dragged him ashore.
- Want a cigarette?
- No.
No smoking on the beach.
But after he came to,
he accused me of diving in to steal his fish.
A year later, he did it again.
But that time, I hesitated.
I stood on the shore watching him
thrash and call for help.
His head bobbed up and down.
The feeling from a year before, limbs trapped, sinking,
choked me again.
So, when you ask if I'd help in a disaster,
I said I didn't know.
Did he die?
No. I rescued him again,
I just hesitated a bit.
But he'd been under too long, choking, and came out simple-minded.
Later his parents knelt to thank me.
After that I stopped swimming.
You think his condition is your fault?
Two minutes less, and he'd be fine?
Two other possibilities.
He doesn't come out simple-minded, but drags you under.
Or you save him and he turns on you again.
Fan Xiao, could you comfort me
like a normal person?
You Shu Lang, you really are a good man.
You said before we have no right to decide
others' life and death.
But as long as we're alive, someone will remind us
the world isn't all bad.
It can be beautiful.
So, you're that someone who tells me the world isn't all bad.
I just want to tell you
each of us has old wounds we can't face.
Avoiding them isn't shameful, nor is it cowardly.
We just need to let go.
Let go.
Don't obsess over whether you can face it.
If you can't face the sea, don't.
If you can't swim, don't.
Fan Xiao, let's go back to the room.
We'll lock the windows and doors, and we won't hear the damn waves.
♫ ♫